Guide to the Tamiment Library Poster and Broadside Collection GRAPHICS.002
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Unprocessed Materials (Flat-file-folder 6, Roll-storage Shared Tamiment 021, Box 8, Folder 1-6, Box 9, Folder 1-8, Box Shared Tamiment 020, Folder 2-9, Box Shared Tamiment 028, Folder 1-3, 10, Box Shared Tamiment 029, Folder 2-3, Box 3, Box 4, Box 6, Box 7, Box 5, Box Shared Tamiment MS002, Flat-file-folder 2, Flat-file-folder 3, Flat-file-folder 1, Flat-file-folder 4, Flat-file-folder 12, Flat-file-folder 9 Right, Flat-file-folder 9, Flat-file-folder 11, Box Shared Tamiment 043, Box Shared Tamiment 048, Folder 9, Box Shared Tamiment 050, Folder 12, Box 12, Box Shared Tamiment 153, Folder 7-9)
- Unprocessed accretion - NPA 2003.094 (Box Shared Tamiment 059)
- Emma Goldman poster, undated (Box Shared Tamiment 043)
- Duplicates (Box Shared Tamiment 152, Folder 2-5, Flat-file-folder 3, Flat-file-folder 1, Flat-file-folder 2)